<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AquaponicsAssistant</string>
    <string name="definition">Aquaponics is the combination of aquaculture (raising fish) and hydroponics (the
soil-less growing of plants) that grows fish and plants together in one integrated
system. The fish waste provides an organic food source for the plants, and the
plants naturally filter the water for the fish.</string>

    <string name="benefits">\n1) Saves Space
\nAquaponics systems allow you to place plants closer to each other than normal which saves a lot of space.

\n\n2) No Weeding
\n Aquaponics systems don’t encourage/favor the growth of weeds because there is no soil.

\n\n3) No Soil Pests
\nAquaponics systems are also beneficial because they don’t harbour soil pests. Soil pests destroy plants. The only way to eliminate soil pests is by using pesticides.


\n\n4) Offers A Source Of Income
 \nselling surplus production of vegetables and fish helps to earn extra income.
\n\n5) Plants Grow Faster
\nThe fact that plants have access to nutrients 24 hours makes them grow faster.
\n\n6) Less Energy
\nAquaponics systems also require less energy. Because there is no weeding, pest control and other measures, you use less energy, approximately 70 percent less energy compared to traditional gardening.

</string>
    <string name="Requirements">\nThe Hardware (materials and equipment needed to build your system)
\n1.Fish tank(s)
\n2.Grow Bed(s) – Media beds, DWC, Wicking beds.

\n3.Plumbing pipe and fittings – Will vary depending on number and type of grow beds, system layout and other factors.
\n4.Water Pump – Size depends on desired tank exchange rate, pump head height, number of grow beds, plumbing lengths, widths and number of fittings.
\n\nThe Software (supplies needed to manage and optimize your system)
\n1.Water Quality Test Kit – Our Master API kit is a simple affordable kit to test critical water quality parameters
\n2.pH Adjusters – Adjusting pH in aquaponics is a necessary part of managing a system and there are specific pH adjusters that are only suitable for aquaponics.

\n3.Gardening Supplies – Items such as pruning shears, gloves, sprayers and more.
\n4.Pest Management Supplies – There are a variety of pests that can impact your plants and there are very specific aquaponic safe products that should only be used in your system.

    </string>

    <string name="FAQ">\n\nQuestion:Is it more efficient or faster than a regular soil garden?
\nAnswer:Yes. It is about twice as fast as a soil garden and you can plant much closer together. In a normal garden, the nutrients are in the soil and in our system, the nutrients are in the water. Planting close together is not a bad thing at all.

\n\nQuestion:How much trouble is it to maintain?
\nAnswer:Once everything is set up, is very simple. Daily maintenance is feeding the fish, checking the plants for insects and making sure that all your pumps are running correctly.
    \n\nQuestion:How much power does it use?
    \nAnswer:The water pump and air pump together use 23 watts. An additional air pump would be needed for the Sanctuary 96 or 128 and would use another 6 watts.
    </string>
    <string-array name="Options">
        <item>What is Aquaponics?</item>
        <item>Benefits of Aquaponics</item>
        <item>Requirements</item>
        <item>Online Resources</item>
        <item>Community</item>
        <item>FAQ</item>
        <item>Seed Tracker</item>
        <item>Log Out</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
